Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 31, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 31, Folder 138)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 138)
- Box: 31, Folder: 139, Publication (Box 31, Folder 139)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 139)
- Box: 31, Folder: 140, Publication (Box 31, Folder 140)
  - Item 1: You and Your Job, 1968; Publication (Box 31, Folder 140)
- Box: 31, Folder: 141, Publication (Box 31, Folder 141)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1975; Publication (Box 31, Folder 141)
- Box: 31, Folder: 142, Publication (Box 31, Folder 142)
  - Item 1: Educational Opportunities, 1948; Publication (Box 31, Folder 142)
- Box: 31, Folder: 143, Publication (Box 31, Folder 143)
  - Item 1: Basic Introductory Information, 1973; Publication (Box 31, Folder 143)
- Box: 31, Folder: 144, Publication (Box 31, Folder 144)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations, 1973; Publication (Box 31, Folder 144)
- Box: 31, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 31, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Chart, 1976; Publication (Box 31, Folder 145)
- Box: 31, Folder: 146, Publication (Box 31, Folder 146)
  - Item 1: Industrial Organization Charts, 1952; Publication (Box 31, Folder 146)
- Box: 31, Folder: 147, Publication (Box 31, Folder 147)
  - Item 1: Organizations Charts, 1953; Publication (Box 31, Folder 147)
- Box: 31, Folder: 148, Publication (Box 31, Folder 148)
  - Item 1: Standard Practice Manual, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 148)
- Box: 31, Folder: 149, Publication (Box 31, Folder 149)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1963; Publication (Box 31, Folder 149)
- Box: 31, Folder: 150, Publication (Box 31, Folder 150)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of Wawasset Beneficial Society, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 150)
- Box: 31, Folder: 151, Publication (Box 31, Folder 151)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 31, Folder 151)
- Box: 31, Folder: 152, Publication (Box 31, Folder 152)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurable Benefits, 1970; Publication (Box 31, Folder 152)
- Box: 31, Folder: 153, Publication (Box 31, Folder 153)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1966; Publication (Box 31, Folder 153)
- Box: 31, Folder: 154, Publication (Box 31, Folder 154)
  - Item 1: Wage Rates, 1965; Publication (Box 31, Folder 154)
- Box: 31, Folder: 155, Publication (Box 31, Folder 155)
  - Item 1: Constitution and By-Laws of Wawasset Beneficial Society, 1964; Publication (Box 31, Folder 155)
- Box: 31, Folder: 156, Publication (Box 31, Folder 156)
  - Item 1: General Safety Rules, 1956; Publication (Box 31, Folder 156)
- Box: 31, Folder: 157, Publication (Box 31, Folder 157)
  - Item 1: Personnel Department, 1951; Publication (Box 31, Folder 157)
- Box: 31, Folder: 158, Publication (Box 31, Folder 158)
  - Item 1: Management Training Course, 1954; Publication (Box 31, Folder 158)
- Box: 31, Folder: 159, Publication (Box 31, Folder 159)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Courses, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 159)
- Box: 31, Folder: 160, Publication (Box 31, Folder 160)
  - Item 1: Plants And Equipment & Other Pertinent Data, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 160)
- Box: 31, Folder: 161, Publication (Box 31, Folder 161)
  - Item 1: Schedule For College Graduate Trainees, 1950; Publication (Box 31, Folder 161)
- Box: 32, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Introduction Training Center, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Box: 32, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Management Inventory and Development Program, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Box: 32, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Wage Incentives, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Box: 32, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification and Suggestion System, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Box: 32, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Inventory and Development Program, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Box: 32, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Time and Motion Study, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Box: 32, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Box: 32, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Box: 32, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Box: 32, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Group Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Box: 32, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Time and Motion Study, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Box: 32, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Summary of The Marathon Management Practice Program, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Box: 32, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Tellers Instructions, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Box: 32, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Job Classification, 1970; Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Box: 32, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Management Development, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Box: 32, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Box: 32, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Sales Training Notes, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Box: 32, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Fire Brigade Manual, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Box: 32, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification Proposal, Publication (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Box: 32, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1954; Publication (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Box: 32, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Merchandise Arithmetic, 1958; Publication (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Box: 32, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Outline of Principles of Department Store Management Course, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Box: 32, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Sales and Service Conference, 1958; Publication (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Box: 32, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Initial Training Program, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Box: 32, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Course For Assistant Section Managers, 1958; Publication (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Box: 32, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology No. 27, 1959; Publication (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Box: 32, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Box: 32, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Training, 1964; Publication (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Box: 32, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Training For New and Pre-Supervisors, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 29)
- Box: 32, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Management Inventory and Development Program, 1954; Publication (Box 32, Folder 30)
- Box: 32, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Group Major Medical Expense Insurance Plan Certificate Non-Occupational Coverage, Publication (Box 32, Folder 31)
- Box: 32, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Wage Payment System, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Box: 32, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Box: 32, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification & Suggestion System, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Box: 32, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Employee Attitudes, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 35)
- Box: 32, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Payroll Procedure, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Box: 32, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Industry Fellowship Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 37)
- Box: 32, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Training System, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Box: 32, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1952; Publication (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Box: 32, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Development Training Program For College Graduates, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 40)
- Box: 32, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Rating Report, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 41)
- Box: 32, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Report To The Board Of Directors, 1952; Publication (Box 32, Folder 42)
- Box: 32, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Report To The Board Of Directors, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 43)
- Box: 32, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Organizations, 1952; Publication (Box 32, Folder 44)
- Box: 32, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Engineering and Manufacturing Training Program, 1956; Publication (Box 32, Folder 45)
- Box: 32, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Skilled Trades Training Program, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 46)
- Box: 32, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Sales Divisions With Branch & Distributor Territories, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 47)
- Box: 32, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Marketing Organization, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 48)
- Box: 32, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Industrial Relations Organization, 1970; Publication (Box 32, Folder 49)
- Box: 32, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 50)
- Box: 32, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 51)
- Box: 32, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 52)
- Box: 32, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Suggestion System, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 53)
- Box: 32, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Standards, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 54)
- Box: 32, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Educational Assistance Program, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 55)
- Box: 32, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Box: 32, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Policy and Procedure For The Maytag Employee's Idea Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 32, Folder 57)
- Box: 32, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification News, 1970; Publication (Box 32, Folder 58)
- Box: 32, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 59)
- Box: 32, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Engineering Program, 1963; Publication (Box 32, Folder 60)
- Box: 32, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plans For Hourly Paid Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 32, Folder 61)
- Box: 32, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Pension and Insurance Plans For Hourly Paid Employees, 1958; Publication (Box 32, Folder 62)
- Box: 32, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Employee's Handbook, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 63)
- Box: 32, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Relief and Benefit Association Handbook, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 64)
- Box: 32, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Relief and Benefit Association Handbook, 1960; Publication (Box 32, Folder 65)
- Box: 32, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Retirement Life Insurance Plans, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 66)
- Box: 32, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Employee Information Kit, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 67)
- Box: 32, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Retirement Life Insurance Plans, 1963; Publication (Box 32, Folder 68)
- Box: 32, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Program, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 69)
- Box: 32, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Your Salary Continuance Program, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 70)
- Box: 32, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Educational Assistance Plan, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 71)
- Box: 32, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 72)
- Box: 32, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Engineering Co-Op Program, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 73)
- Box: 32, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1966; Publication (Box 32, Folder 74)
- Box: 32, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Engineering and Manufacturing, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 75)
- Box: 32, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Training Program, 1953; Publication (Box 32, Folder 76)
- Box: 32, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Retirement and Life Insurance Plans, 1957; Publication (Box 32, Folder 77)
- Box: 32, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Pension, Savings Plans and Benefits, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 78)
- Box: 32, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Employee Information and Benefits, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 79)
- Box: 32, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Manual, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 80)
- Box: 32, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Work Simplification, 1971; Publication (Box 32, Folder 81)
- Box: 32, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Personal Administration, 1965; Publication (Box 32, Folder 82)
- Box: 32, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Management Development Policy, 1964; Publication (Box 32, Folder 83)
- Box: 32, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting Part 1, 1968; Publication (Box 32, Folder 84)
- Box: 32, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1967; Publication (Box 32, Folder 85)
- Box: 33, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Training, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Box: 33, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Administrative Payroll: Policy and Procedure Manual, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Box: 33, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Payroll Manual For Departmental Supervisors, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Box: 33, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Information For Employees Supplemental Benefit Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Box: 33, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Working Foreman Evaluation, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Box: 33, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Working Foreman Planning Manual, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Box: 33, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Conference Leadership and Developing Coaching Techniques For Supervision, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Box: 33, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Development Coaching, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Box: 33, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Proposed Industrial Engineering Co-opt Program, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Box: 33, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Job Analysis, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Box: 33, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Box: 33, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Introduction Training Manual, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Box: 33, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Engineering & Manufacturing Training Program, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Box: 33, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Job Instruction Training Outline, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Box: 33, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Apprenticeship Program, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Box: 33, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Box: 33, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Box: 33, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Accident Prevention, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Box: 33, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Organizations Charts, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Box: 33, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Grievance Forms, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Box: 33, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Personnel Forms, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Box: 33, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Box: 33, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Educational Assistance Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Box: 33, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Personnel Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Box: 33, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Employee Recruiting, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Box: 33, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Box: 33, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Unified Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Box: 33, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Box: 33, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Medical Care, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Box: 33, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Record Of New Medical Expenses, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Box: 33, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Group Plan Of Major Medical Expense Insurance, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Box: 33, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Medical Service, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Box: 33, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Vacations, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Box: 33, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Suggestion Systems, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Box: 33, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Wage and Policy For All Employees Paid On An Hourly or Piece Work Basis, 1945; Publication (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Box: 33, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1973; Publication (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Box: 33, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Long Term Disability Insurance, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Box: 33, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1970; Publication (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Box: 33, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Commencement Exercises and Orientation Program, 1970; Publication (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Box: 33, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Retirement Years-A Reading List, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Box: 33, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Newsletter, 1970; Publication (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Box: 33, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Rating, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Box: 33, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: New Employees, 1970; Publication (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Box: 33, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Retirement Income Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Box: 33, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Employee Retirement Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Box: 33, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Management Development Program, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Box: 33, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Manpower Development For Wholesale Management, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Box: 33, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: National Sales Impact, 1956; Publication (Box 33, Folder 48)
- Box: 33, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Trainee Manual, Publication (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Box: 33, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Employee Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 33, Folder 50)
- Box: 33, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Appraisal of Employee Performance Outline of The Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 51)
- Box: 33, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Employee Skills Inventory, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 52)
- Box: 33, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Successful Applicant Award, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Box: 33, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Normal Disability Benefits For Any One Service Year, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 54)
- Box: 33, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Tabulating Information, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 55)
- Box: 33, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Major Medical Expense Certificate, 1963; Publication (Box 33, Folder 56)
- Box: 33, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Personnel Relations Recruitment and Selection, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 57)
- Box: 33, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Member Identification Card, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 58)
- Box: 33, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 59)
- Box: 33, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Employee's Withholding Exemption Certificate, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 60)
- Box: 33, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Successful Applicant Award, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 61)
- Box: 33, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 62)
- Box: 33, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Introduction of New Employees, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 63)
- Box: 33, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: College Recruiting, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 64)
- Box: 33, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Executive Personnel Bulletin No.30, 1954; Publication (Box 33, Folder 65)
- Box: 33, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Unified Medical Expense Insurance Enrollment Form, 1964; Publication (Box 33, Folder 66)
- Box: 33, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Employee Skills Inventory, 1967; Publication (Box 33, Folder 67)
- Box: 33, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Job Evaluation, 1961; Publication (Box 33, Folder 68)